Guide to the Mabou Mines Archive, 1966-2000 (bulk 1970-1995) MSS.133
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series VII: Production Books, 146155
  Series VII is made up of the contents of binders and folders that variously comprised scripts, notes, cues, contact sheets, schedules, and the like, usually heavily annotated, often compiled by a stage manager or director, for use during production of a play. Several Mabou Mines' productions, and some Mabou Mines-affiliated productions, are represented. Some folders contain scripts the company did not file with those scripts that make up Series VI. There is also significant overlap with Series III: Production Files. Of particular interest are the contents of binders used by JoAnne Akalaitis during production of the Dead End Kids film.
  Boxes stored offsite: Box 37 - Barcode: 31142042235971 Box 38 - Barcode: 31142042235989 Box 39 - Barcode: 31142042235997
  - The Balcony binder, undated; 146231 (Box 37, Folder 1383)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142042235971
  - The B. Beaver Animation lighting script, undated; 146230 (Box 37, Folder 1384)
  - The B. Beaver Animation lighting cues, Shiva Theatre/Public, undated; 146229 (Box 37, Folder 1385)
  - The B. Beaver Animation stage manager's book; May 1990, 146228 (Box 37, Folder 1386)
  - Cold Harbor stage manager's script; Nov 6, 1984, 146227 (Box 37, Folder 1387)
  - Cold Harbor Bryan's movement script, undated; 146226 (Box 37, Folder 1388)
  - Cold Harbor lighting script, 1983; 146225 (Box 37, Folder 1389)
  - Cold Harbor Paris binder, script with cues, undated; 146224 (Box 37, Folder 1390)
  - Cold Harbor stage manager scripts, undated; 146223 (Box 37, Folder 1391)
  - Dead End Kids script with cues, Public Theater; June 2-20, 1982, 146222 (Box 37, Folder 1392)
  - Dead End Kids stage manager's script (Public), 1982; 146221 (Box 37, Folder 1393)
  - Dead End Kids film, JoAnne Akalaitis's book, part 1, undated; 146220 (Box 37, Folder 1394)
  - Dead End Kids film, JoAnne Akalaitis's book, part 2, undated; 146219 (Box 37, Folder 1395)
  - Dead End Kids film, reels notes, undated; 146218 (Box 37, Folder 1396)
  - Dressed Like an Egg binder, undated; 146217 (Box 37, Folder 1397)
  - Eager Witness script, Rosemary Moore, undated; 146216 (Box 37, Folder 1398)
  - Flow My Tears, The Policeman Said binder, 1985; 146215 (Box 37, Folder 1399)
  - Flow My Tears, The Policeman Said binder, undated; 146214 (Box 37, Folder 1400)
  - Help Wanted binder, part 1, 1986; 146213 (Box 37, Folder 1401)
  - Help Wanted binder, part 2, 1986; 146212 (Box 37, Folder 1402)
  - In the Jungle of Cities calling script, undated; 146211 (Box 37, Folder 1403)
  - In the Jungle of Cities script with letter; Jan 14, 1991, 146210 (Box 37, Folder 1404)
  - In the Jungle of Cities stage manager's script, undated; 146209 (Box 37, Folder 1405)
  - It's a Man's World video master script, 1985; 146208 (Box 37, Folder 1406)
  - It's a Man's World binder: "MASTER", part 1, 1985; 146207 (Box 37, Folder 1407)
  - It's a Man's World binder: "MASTER", part 2, 1985; 146206 (Box 37, Folder 1408)
  - It's a Man's World lighting script; Dec 1986, 146205 (Box 37, Folder 1409)
  - It's a Man's World modified script, 1987; 146204 (Box 37, Folder 1410)
  - It's a Man's World sound cues, script, 1987; 146203 (Box 37, Folder 1411)
  - It's a Man's World tech script; video cues, 1987; 146202 (Box 37, Folder 1412)
  - It's a Man's World tech script copy; July 10, 1987, 146201 (Box 37, Folder 1413)
  - Lear original PSM book, part 1, undated; 146200 (Box 37, Folder 1414)
  - Lear original PSM book, part 2, undated; 146199 (Box 37, Folder 1415)
  - Lear E. Valsing binder, part 1, undated; 146198 (Box 38, Folder 1416)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142042235989
  - Lear E. Valsing binder, part 2, undated; 146197 (Box 38, Folder 1417)
  - Lear E. Valsing binder, part 3, undated; 146196 (Box 38, Folder 1418)
  - Lear NYC rehearsal, Tony Gerber's binder, part 1, undated; 146195 (Box 38, Folder 1419)
  - Lear NYC rehearsal, Tony Gerber's binder, part 2, undated; 146194 (Box 38, Folder 1420)
  - Lear NYC rehearsal, Tony Gerber's binder, part 3, undated; 146193 (Box 38, Folder 1421)
  - Lear NYC rehearsal, Tony Gerber's binder, part 4, undated; 146192 (Box 38, Folder 1422)
  - Lear sound binder, part 1, undated; 146191 (Box 38, Folder 1423)
  - Lear sound binder, part 2, undated; 146190 (Box 38, Folder 1424)
  - Lear sound binder, part 3, undated; 146189 (Box 38, Folder 1425)
  - Lear Storm King, stage manager book, undated; 146188 (Box 38, Folder 1426)
  - Lear Jack Doulin's binder, undated; 146187 (Box 38, Folder 1427)
  - Lear script with cuts, part 1, undated; 146186 (Box 38, Folder 1428)
  - Lear script with cuts, part 2, undated; 146185 (Box 38, Folder 1429)
  - Lear script with cuts, part 3, undated; 146184 (Box 38, Folder 1430)
  - Lear script with cuts, part 4, undated; 146183 (Box 38, Folder 1431)
  - Lear ASM (Allison Astor) notebook; NYC, Toronto; part 1, 1990; 146182 (Box 38, Folder 1432)
  - Lear ASM (Allison Astor) notebook; NYC, Toronto; part 2, 1990; 146181 (Box 38, Folder 1433)
  - The MahabharANTa video, undated; 146180 (Box 38, Folder 1434)
  - Phaedra binder, 1986; 146179 (Box 38, Folder 1435)
  - Pretty Boy sound script, undated; 146178 (Box 38, Folder 1436)
  - Reel to Real stage manager's script, undated; 146177 (Box 38, Folder 1437)
  - Sueños binder, undated; 146176 (Box 38, Folder 1438)
  - Sueños score, 1989; 146175 (Box 38, Folder 1439)
  - Sueños assistant stage manager's notebook" [binder], undated; 146174 (Box 38, Folder 1440)
  - Sueños Triplex Theater; assistant stage manager's notebook, undated; 146173 (Box 38, Folder 1441)
  - Sueños director's script; Hasty Pudding; April 2, 1988, 146172 (Box 38, Folder 1442)
  - Sueños binder; Hasty Pudding, 1988; 146171 (Box 38, Folder 1443)
  - Sueños nuArts binder, part 1, undated; 146170 (Box 38, Folder 1444)
  - Sueños nuArts binder, part 2, undated; 146169 (Box 38, Folder 1445)
  - Sueños nuArts binder, part 3, undated; 146168 (Box 38, Folder 1446)
  - Through the Leaves Allison Dubin's binder, 1986; 146167 (Box 39, Folder 1447)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142042235997
  - Through the Leaves binder, undated; 146166 (Box 39, Folder 1448)
  - Through the Leaves prompt script, undated; 146165 (Box 39, Folder 1449)
  - Through the Leaves production notes binder, part 1, 1984; 146164 (Box 39, Folder 1450)
  - Through the Leaves production notes binder, part 2, 1984; 146163 (Box 39, Folder 1451)
  - Through the Leaves production notes binder, part 3, 1984; 146162 (Box 39, Folder 1452)
  - Through the Leaves production notes binder, part 4, 1984; 146161 (Box 39, Folder 1453)
  - Worstward Ho stage manager's script [binder], undated; 146160 (Box 39, Folder 1454)
  - Worstward Ho binder, undated; 146159 (Box 39, Folder 1455)
  - Worstward Ho light cue script, undated; 146158 (Box 39, Folder 1456)
  - Worstward Ho stage manager's script, 1986; 146157 (Box 39, Folder 1457)
  - Worstward Ho tech script; Sept, 1986, 146156 (Box 39, Folder 1458)
- Series VIII: Touring Files, 145990
  This series comprises records of Mabou Mines performances outside of New York City, including multi-state and international tours. The bulk of the series spans the 1980s into the early 1990s.
  Subseries A contains files relating to specific performances or tours of specific productions. Cold Harbor is especially well-represented here, as this production toured extensively in the mid-1980s. Most of the folders in Subseries A contain some combination of the following materials: correspondence with representatives of a venue; tour schedules and itineraries; contact information of cast, crew, and venue; financial records including budgets; contracts; programs and flyers; lighting plots, track sheets, and cues; ground plans and stage schematics of various venues; maps and other travel information. The folders are arranged chronologically by performance date. The files within each folder may date to several months before and/or after the performance date. This arrangement clearly shows that it was not unusual for several Mabou Mines productions to tour simultaneously. There is significant overlap with the materials in Series III: Production Files, and this subseries can be compared with Series II: Programs for a more complete record of Mabou Mines performances.
  Subseries B, General Touring Files, comprises similar material (correspondence, financial records, technical specifications, etc) related to no production in particular, or related to many different productions. This series is rich in what the company called "touring inquiries." Subseries C contains information on travel discounts including airline miles programs, and information on travel and lodging in specific cities. Subseries D contains Mabou Mines' collection of information on various national and international theater organizations and festivals, some in which Mabou Mines took part. These folders are arranged in alphabetical order by organization, then by festival.
  Boxes stored offsite: Box 40 - Barcode: 31142042236003 Box 41 - Barcode: 31142042236011 Box 42 - Barcode: 31142042236029 Box 43 - Barcode: 31142042236037 Box 138 - Barcode: 31142042236227
  - Subseries A: Touring Files by Production, 146049
    - Vanishing Pictures Feb-Mar, 1980; financial reports, 146154 (Box 40, Folder 1459)
      Offsite Barcode: 31142042236003
    - A Prelude to Death in Venice July 2-25, 1980; Public Theater, 146153 (Box 40, Folder 1460)
    - A Prelude to Death in Venice Aug 1980; West Coast tour, 146152 (Box 40, Folder 1461)
    - A Prelude to Death in Venice Oct 1-5, 1980; Theater 140, Brussels, 146151 (Box 40, Folder 1462)
    - A Prelude to Death in Venice Oct 6-12, 1980; American Center, Paris, 146150 (Box 40, Folder 1463)
    - A Prelude to Death in Venice Oct 20-26, 1980; Milan, 146149 (Box 40, Folder 1464)
    - Four Radio Plays ZBS Sound Exhibition, Fort Edward, NY, 1980-1981; 146148 (Box 40, Folder 1465)
    - Vanishing Pictures Jan 1981; Oberlin College, Ohio, 146147 (Box 40, Folder 1466)
    - A Prelude to Death in Venice Mar 1981; Walker Art Center, Minneapolis, MN, 146146 (Box 40, Folder 1467)
    - A Prelude to Death in Venice Mar 1981; Simon Fraser University, British Columbia, 146145 (Box 40, Folder 1468)
    - A Prelude to Death in Venice Mar 1981; Grinnell College, Iowa, 146144 (Box 40, Folder 1469)
    - A Prelude to Death in Venice Mar 1981; Portland, OR, 146143 (Box 40, Folder 1470)
    - A Prelude to Death in Venice Apr 1981; UC Santa Cruz see also OS for poster, 146142 (Box 40, Folder 1471)
    - A Prelude to Death in Venice Apr 1981; University of Marland/Baltimore County, 146141 (Box 40, Folder 1472)
    - Dead End Kids May 1981; Toronto Theatre Festival includes festival program, 146140 (Box 40, Folder 1473)
    - Dead End Kids May 1981; Tortonto law suit, 146139 (Box 40, Folder 1474)
    - A Prelude to Death in Venice July-Aug 1981; Brazil, 146138 (Box 40, Folder 1475)
    - Come and Go / The Lost Ones Oct 4-11, 1981; Paris, 146137 (Box 40, Folder 1476)
    - Dead End Kids Mar 2-7, 1982; Wilwaukee, WI, 146136 (Box 40, Folder 1477)
    - Dead End Kids Mar 8-14, 1982; Walker Art Center, Minneapolis, MN, 146135 (Box 40, Folder 1478)
    - Dead End Kids Mar 17-22, 1982; Seattle, WA, 146134 (Box 40, Folder 1479)
    - Hajj May 11-30, 1982; Performing Garage, NYC, 146133 (Box 40, Folder 1480)
    - Hajj [one] June 10-12, 1982; AFI Video Festival, Washington, DC, 146132 (Box 40, Folder 1481)
    - Company June 25-27, 1982; PS 122, 146131 (Box 40, Folder 1482)
    - A Prelude to Death in Venice Aug 24-Sep 5, 1982; Traverse Theatre, Edinburgh, Scotland, 146130 (Box 40, Folder 1483)
    - A Prelude to Death in Venice Sep 7-19, 1982; Riverside Studios, London, 146129 (Box 40, Folder 1484)
    - The Lost Ones Sep 27, 1982; Walker Art Center, Minneapolis, MN, 146128 (Box 40, Folder 1485)
    - Dead End Kids Midwest tour, 1982; 146127 (Box 40, Folder 1486)
    - Dead End Kids Spoleto Festival, Charleston, SC, 1982-1983; 146126 (Box 40, Folder 1487)
    - A Prelude to Death in Venice Feb 3-5, 1983; Greensboro, NC, 146125 (Box 40, Folder 1488)
    - Dead End Kids Feb 23-27, 1983; Annenberg Center, Philadelphia, PA, 146124 (Box 40, Folder 1489)
    - Dead End Kids Feb 23-27, 1983; Annenberg Center, Philadelphia, PA includes program, 146123 (Box 40, Folder 1490)
    - Dead End Kids May 5-15, 1983; PAND Caravan tour, 146122 (Box 40, Folder 1491)
    - A Prelude to Death in Venice May 22-24, 1983; Quebec City, Quebec, 146121 (Box 40, Folder 1492)
    - Company Aug 1983; Exploratium, San Francisco, 146120 (Box 40, Folder 1493)
    - Cold Harbor 1983-1984 tour, 146119 (Box 40, Folder 1494)
    - Dead End Kids 1983-1984; Los Angeles, 146118 (Box 40, Folder 1495)
    - Cold Harbor Apr 1984; Paris, 146117 (Box 40, Folder 1496)
    - A Prelude to Death in Venice / Hajj Aug 1984; Japan tour, part 1 see also OS for maps, 146116 (Box 40, Folder 1497)
    - A Prelude to Death in Venice / Hajj Aug 1984; Japan tour, part 2 see also OS for maps, 146115 (Box 40, Folder 1498)
    - Cold Harbor Nov 1984; National Portrait Gallery, 146114 (Box 40, Folder 1499)
    - Cold Harbor Nov 1984; National Portrait Gallery programs, 146113 (Box 40, Folder 1500)
    - Cold Harbor Nov 1984; SUNY Purchase, 146112 (Box 40, Folder 1501)
    - Through the Leaves 1984-1985; Montreal, 146111 (Box 41, Folder 1502)
      Offsite Barcode: 31142042236011
    - A Prelude to Death in Venice Spring 1985; New England, 146110 (Box 41, Folder 1503)
    - Company Mar 29-30, 1985; University of Massachusetts at Amherst, 146109 (Box 41, Folder 1504)
    - Cold Harbor Aug 1-4, 1985; Kent State University packing list, itinerary, 146108 (Box 41, Folder 1505)
    - Cold Harbor Aug 1-4, 1985; Kent State University see also OS for maps, 146107 (Box 41, Folder 1506)
    - Cold Harbor Fall 1985 tour itinerary, contracts, etc, 146106 (Box 41, Folder 1507)
    - Cold Harbor Fall 1985 tour contract forms, 146105 (Box 41, Folder 1508)
    - Cold Harbor Fall 1985 tour budget, 146104 (Box 41, Folder 1509)
    - Cold Harbor Oct 1985; Stockton State College, NJ, 146103 (Box 41, Folder 1510)
    - Cold Harbor Oct 1985; Stockton State College, NJ lighting; see also OS for plots, 146102 (Box 41, Folder 1511)
    - Cold Harbor Oct 1985; Owensboro, KY, 146101 (Box 41, Folder 1512)
    - Cold Harbor Oct 1985; Owensboro, KY lighting; see also OS for plots, 146100 (Box 41, Folder 1513)
    - Cold Harbor Oct 17-18, 1985; University of Tennessee, Chattanooga see also OS for map, 146099 (Box 41, Folder 1514)
    - Cold Harbor Oct 17-18, 1985; University of Tennessee, Chattanooga lighting; see also OS for plot, 146098 (Box 41, Folder 1515)
    - Cold Harbor Nov 1985; Bardavon 1869 Opera House, Poughkeepse, NY, 146097 (Box 41, Folder 1516)
    - Cold Harbor Nov 1985; Bardavon 1869 Opera House, Poughkeepse, NY lighting; see also OS for track sheets, 146096 (Box 41, Folder 1517)
    - Cold Harbor Nov 1985; Hartford, CT see also OS for maps, etc, 146095 (Box 41, Folder 1518)
    - Cold Harbor Nov 1985; Hartford, CT lighting; see also OS for plot, 146094 (Box 41, Folder 1519)
    - Cold Harbor Nov 1985; Keane, NH, 146093 (Box 41, Folder 1520)
    - Cold Harbor Nov 1985; Catamount, St. Johnsbury, VT, 146092 (Box 41, Folder 1521)
    - Cold Harbor Nov 1985; Catamount, St. Johnsbury, VT lighting; see also OS for plot, 146091 (Box 41, Folder 1522)
    - Cold Harbor Nov 1985; Univerisity of Massachusetts at Amherst, 146090 (Box 41, Folder 1523)
    - Cold Harbor Nov 1985; Univerisity of Massachusetts at Amherst lighting; see also OS for plot, 146089 (Box 41, Folder 1524)
    - Cold Harbor Nov 1985; Northeastern University, Boston, MA, 146088 (Box 41, Folder 1525)
    - Cold Harbor Nov 1985; Northeastern University, Boston, MA lighting, 146087 (Box 41, Folder 1526)
    - Cold Harbor Nov 1985; Dartmouth, Hanover, NH, 146086 (Box 41, Folder 1527)
    - various productions 1986 financial records, 146085 (Box 41, Folder 1528)
    - Cold Harbor 1986 tech specs, 146084 (Box 41, Folder 1529)
    - Cold Harbor Spring 1986 tour itinerary, contracts, etc, 146083 (Box 41, Folder 1530)
    - Cold Harbor Spring 1986 tour itinerary; includes flyers and Prelude… 8x10 print, 146082 (Box 41, Folder 1531)
    - Cold Harbor Feb-Mar 1986; Atlanta, GA, 146081 (Box 41, Folder 1532)
    - Cold Harbor Feb-Mar 1986; Atlanta, GA lighting; see also OS for plot, 146080 (Box 41, Folder 1533)
    - Cold Harbor Mar 11, 1986; University of Vermont, Burlington, 146079 (Box 41, Folder 1534)
    - Cold Harbor Mar 11, 1986; University of Vermont, Burlington lighting; see also OS for plot, track sheets, 146078 (Box 41, Folder 1535)
    - Cold Harbor Mar 14, 1986; Williams College, Williamstown, MA, 146077 (Box 41, Folder 1536)
    - Cold Harbor Mar 14, 1986; Williams College, Williamstown, MA lighting; see also OS for plot, track sheets, 146076 (Box 41, Folder 1537)
    - Cold Harbor Mar 26-30, 1986; Charleston, SC, 146075 (Box 41, Folder 1538)
    - Cold Harbor Mar 26-30, 1986; Charleston, SC lighting; see also OS for plot, track sheets, 146074 (Box 41, Folder 1539)
    - Imagination Dead Imagine Sep 1986; Iowa City tech specs, 146073 (Box 41, Folder 1540)
    - Cold Harbor [Sep] 1986; Kansas City, MO, 146072 (Box 41, Folder 1541)
    - Cold Harbor Sep-Oct 1986; University of Iowa, Iowa City lighting, 146071 (Box 41, Folder 1542)
    - Cold Harbor [Sep-Oct?] 1986; Southwest Missouri State University, Springfield, MO lighting; see also OS for plots, track sheets, 146070 (Box 41, Folder 1543)
    - Company Oct 1986; Iowa City, 146069 (Box 41, Folder 1544)
    - Cold Harbor Oct 7, 1986; University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign lighting; see also OS for plot, track sheets, 146068 (Box 42, Folder 1545)
      Offsite Barcode: 31142042236029
    - Cold Harbor Nov-Dec 1986; UC Davis see also OS for plots, charts, 146067 (Box 42, Folder 1546)
    - Cold Harbor Nov-Dec 1986; Humboldt State University, Arcata, CA see also OS for plots, 146066 (Box 42, Folder 1547)
    - Cold Harbor 1987 tech specs, 146065 (Box 42, Folder 1548)
    - Imagination Dead Imagine Apr 1987; Tallahassee, FL, 146064 (Box 42, Folder 1549)
    - Cold Harbor May 1987; Valladolid, Spain, 146063 (Box 42, Folder 1550)
    - Cold Harbor May 1987; Valladolid, Spain, 146062 (Box 42, Folder 1551)
    - Cold Harbor May 1987; Valladolid, Spain sample press kit, 146061 (Box 42, Folder 1552)
    - Cold Harbor May 1987; Valladolid, Spain see also OS, 146060 (Box 42, Folder 1553)
    - Cold Harbor Aug 1987; Philadelphia, 146059 (Box 42, Folder 1554)
    - Company Sep 22-25, 1987; University of Texas at Austin, 146058 (Box 42, Folder 1555)
    - A Prelude to Death in Venice Sep 22, 1987; Ohio Wesleyan University, 146057 (Box 42, Folder 1556)
    - A Prelude to Death in Venice Sep 25, 1987; Oberlin College, Ohio, 146056 (Box 42, Folder 1557)
    - A Prelude to Death in Venice Oct 9-10, 1987; St. Louis, MO, 146055 (Box 42, Folder 1558)
    - A Prelude to Death in Venice Oct 9-10, 1987; St. Louis, MO, 146054 (Box 42, Folder 1559)
    - Cold Harbor 1988 film files, 146053 (Box 42, Folder 1560)
    - Cold Harbor 1989 tech specs (freight), 146052 (Box 42, Folder 1561)
    - Help Wanted Jan 1989, 146051 (Box 42, Folder 1562)
    - Cold Harbor June 1989; District Curators, Washington, DC, 146050 (Box 42, Folder 1563)
  - Subseries B: General Touring Files, 146035
    - touring correspondence, information, 1981-1985; 146048 (Box 42, Folder 1564)
    - touring pack, 1982-1983; 146047 (Box 42, Folder 1565)
    - international touring correspondence, 1984-1987; 146046 (Box 42, Folder 1566)
    - tour information; publicity package, 1985-1986; 146045 (Box 42, Folder 1567)
    - miscellaneous touring files, 1986-1989; 146044 (Box 42, Folder 1568)
    - national touring correspondence, information, 1986, 1990; 146043 (Box 42, Folder 1569)
    - touring correspondence, 1988-1991; 146042 (Box 42, Folder 1570)
    - touring correspondence, 1990, 1993; 146041 (Box 42, Folder 1571)
    - international touring correspondence, information, 1990-1991; 146040 (Box 42, Folder 1572)
    - correspondence, 1991; 146039 (Box 42, Folder 1573)
    - touring inquiries, contact information, 1991; 146038 (Box 42, Folder 1574)
    - touring inquiries, 1991-1992; 146037 (Box 42, Folder 1575)
    - touring inquiries, 1992; 146036 (Box 42, Folder 1576)
    - general touring files - mailing schedules, administrative notes, presenting org. info, etc., 1991-1994; 151102 (Box 138, Folder 2043)
      Offsite Barcode: 31142042236227
    - correspondence, touring inquiries, 1991-1992; 151103 (Box 138, Folder 2044)
    - contact lists, 1991-1992; 151104 (Box 138, Folder 2045)
    - touring contact memos, 1992-1994; 151105 (Box 138, Folder 2046)
    - touring contact memos, undated [ca. 1992-1994]; 151106 (Box 138, Folder 2047)
    - touring contact memos, undated [ca. 1992-1994]; 151107 (Box 138, Folder 2048)
  - Subseries C: Travel Information, 146024
    - airline miles: Pan Am, 1991; 146034 (Box 42, Folder 1577)
    - airline miles: Delta, 1991-1992; 146033 (Box 42, Folder 1578)
    - airline miles: American Airlines, 1992; 146032 (Box 42, Folder 1579)
    - airline miles: United Airlines, 1992; 146031 (Box 42, Folder 1580)
    - airline miles: Continental, 1992; 146030 (Box 42, Folder 1581)
    - travel discounts, undated; 146029 (Box 42, Folder 1582)
    - Boston, Cambridge, undated; 146028 (Box 42, Folder 1583)
    - Los Angeles, undated; 146027 (Box 42, Folder 1584)
    - Montreal, Quebec, 1983-1984; 146026 (Box 42, Folder 1585)
    - Greece, undated; 146025 (Box 42, Folder 1586)
  - Subseries D: Organizations and Festivals, 145991
    - Arizona Public Service Co., re: "WYIMA", 1994; 146023 (Box 43, Folder 1587)
      Offsite Barcode: 31142042236037
    - International Theatre Institute, 1984, 1986; 146022 (Box 43, Folder 1588)
    - Mid Atlantic States Arts Consortium, undated; 146021 (Box 43, Folder 1589)
    - Sundance Institute, 1988, 1991; 146020 (Box 43, Folder 1590)
    - Western Alliance of Arts Administrators, 1983, 1985; 146019 (Box 43, Folder 1591)
    - Yellow Springs Institute, 1987-1993; 146018 (Box 43, Folder 1592)
    - Autumn Festivals of Barcelona, 1991; 146017 (Box 43, Folder 1593)
    - Belfast Festival at Queens, 1991; 146016 (Box 43, Folder 1594)
    - Belluard-Bollwerk Festival Fribourg, 1988, 1991; 146015 (Box 43, Folder 1595)
    - Blackpool Grand Theatre, 1989-1991; 146014 (Box 43, Folder 1596)
    - Brighton Festival '91, program, 1991; 146013 (Box 43, Folder 1597)
    - Chianti World Festival of Contemporary Drama, 1991; 146012 (Box 43, Folder 1598)
    - De Singel, Belgium, 1986-1987, 1991; 146011 (Box 43, Folder 1599)
    - Dublin International Festival, undated; 146010 (Box 43, Folder 1600)
    - du Maurier World Stage, Harbourfront, 1986-1987; 146009 (Box 43, Folder 1601)
    - Edinburgh International Festival, 1991; 146008 (Box 43, Folder 1602)
    - Hamburg, 1991; 146007 (Box 43, Folder 1603)
    - Hebbel Theatre, Berlin, 1992; 146006 (Box 43, Folder 1604)
    - Mayfest Limited, Scotland, 1991; 146005 (Box 43, Folder 1605)
    - New York International Festival of the Arts, 1988, 1991; 146004 (Box 43, Folder 1606)
    - Orlando International Fringe Festival, 1992; 146003 (Box 43, Folder 1607)
    - Riverside Studios, 1991; 146002 (Box 43, Folder 1608)
    - Samuel Beckett Festival, The Hague, 1991-1992; 146001 (Box 43, Folder 1609)
    - Shaw Theatre, London, 1991; 146000 (Box 43, Folder 1610)
    - Sommerszene '90, catalogue, 1990; 145999 (Box 43, Folder 1611)
    - Tampere International Theatre Festival, Finland, 1992; 145998 (Box 43, Folder 1612)
    - Theaterburo Hannover, 1991; 145997 (Box 43, Folder 1613)
    - Théâtre de la Bastille, 1991; 145996 (Box 43, Folder 1614)
    - Tramway, Scotland, 1991; 145995 (Box 43, Folder 1615)